( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
REPUBLIC OF KOREA ARMY
Born in 2004.
BEST TRAINEE
PRIVATE KANG SEONG-JAE
Wait a second.
"The Best Trainee"?
Is that right?
Well, look at that.
We finally got an ace, huh?
Private Kang Seong-jae. Thank you.
Well.
You've got a good voice
and you're good-looking too.
Back in school, you must've...
- Wait, a cat!
- Huh? What?
What was that?
Hey! What if you scratch up
our new recruit?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Drive carefully.
Be gentle.
Right?
Good grief.
Gosh.
The Best Trainee.
Looking back, my life has always been
a fierce battle.
The villains would attack
at any time and any place
and I was often overwhelmed
by the sheer number of enemies.
But who am I?
A strong warrior of the Republic of Korea
and its strong army!
This war-like life...
has finally made me
into the ultimate warrior...
Private Kang Seong-jae!
Hey.
What do you make of this situation?
This seems very wrong, sir.
Right?
It's not just because
I'm an old fart, is it?
No, not at all, sir.
Kids these days sleep so soundly
without a care in the world.
EPISODE 1
GANGLIM
All right.
This is your home now.
Got it?
Fourth Company, First Battalion.
60th Regiment, 29th Division.
Ganglim Post.
The air is amazing, isn't it?
We've even had guys
cure their eczema here.
Well, since you're the Best Trainee,
so I'm not worried...
But still, military life
with people from all over...
Hey!
Snap out of it.
If you do that again
I'll reach my limit.
Yes, I understand.
Let's go.
Welcome to Ganglim Post.
Salute! Welcome back, sir!
Hey, Tak!
So.
Are you happy
to finally have a subordinate?
I'll have to put him through a test
and size him up first, sir.
Hey, you jerk!
Come on.
At boot camp
he was the Best Trainee. A real ace.
What happened at boot camp
doesn't mean anything out here, sir.
Darn, this punk. You're already...
You're already bossing a junior.
Hey, put that down and come here.
Yes, sir.
The following individual
... shown dedication and spirit
of service to his country...
Man, this is good.
Best Trainee, huh? The very best.
The Best Trainee has arrived.
PSYCHOLOGICAL EVALUATION
FAMILY BACKGROUND?
SINGLE MOTHER
Who's on the duty roster today?
IS YOUR FAMILY HARMONIOUS?
AVERAGE
It's not out yet.
FAMILY'S MONTHLY INCOME?
LESS THAN 1.8 MILLION WON
Hey, Best Trainee.
Private Kang Seong-jae.
No need to lie.
Be honest, write down every detail.
Even how many pairs of underwear.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
Sit down.
- Hey, Tak.
- Private First Class Tak Mun-ik.
- Did you put out the makgeolli?
- Yes, sir. I put it in the mess.
Anything to report?
No, sir. Nothing.
FELT LOSS OR DEPRESSION RECENTLY?
YES
Welcome, Private.
Hero.
Private Kang Seong-jae!
What are you doing?
Didn't you just call me, sir?
- Master Sergeant.
- Yeah?
Is it out yet?
Well, about that, sir.
He's...
S-Class, sir.
S-Class? Beyond A-Class?
- S-Class?
- That's a good thing, right?
EXTREMELY HIGH RISK: S
DEPRESSIVE SYMPTOMS
VERY HIGH
GAMING ADDICTION
Salute!
Hey.
I heard the battalion sent an ace,
so I came to check him out.
Is this him?
He's got that fire in his eyes.
What ace?
He's S-Class.
What? There must've been some mix-up.
Damn it. It's not the first time
those jerks sent us their rejects.
Hey.
Private Kang Seong-jae.
To the Room of Truth.
Yes... to the Room of Truth.
PERSONNEL RECORD CARD
KANG SEONG-JAE
What does your mother do?
- She runs a food truck.
- A food truck?
Oh, a street stall.
It's not a stall.
She has an official permit
from the city...
Hey, it's the same thing.
You little punk,
are you playing word games with me?
What's this?
FATHER, KANG YONG-IL
DIED TWO MONTHS PRIOR TO ENLISTMENT
Your father...
passed away recently.
Yes, sir. He passed away two months ago.
Goodness.
That must've been hard on you.
It was all so sudden.
But I'm doing much better now.
Jeez.
What's all this about
being the "Best Trainee"?
More like top priority high-risk soldier.
Hey.
Keep this pinned to your chest
until I say so.
Got it?
When someone talks to you, you answer.
- Yes, sir.
- Goodness, you're frustrating.
- Hey, Tak!
- Private First Class Tak Mun-ik!
Take him to greet the Outpost Commander.
Tell her
that a tragic hero you can't watch
without crying has arrived.
OUTPOST COMMANDER
FIRST LIEUTENANT CHO YE-RIN
Outpost Commander, may I enter?
Come in.
Salute!
I brought the new recruit, Commander.
All right. Let me see him.
Salute!
Private Kang Seong-jae.
On August 18, 2025, I was ordered to
report here...
Kang Seong-jae has been registered.
Report...
Ordered...
Here...
KANG SEONG-JAE,
ORDINARY SOLDIER, AGE 22
COMMEMORATING THE 70TH ANNIVERSARY
OF THE ROK ARMY
Where are you looking?
I'm sorry, I must have
seen something wrong.
I don't know what's up with him.
He says he sees and hears things.
Everyone seems fine on the outside
but they start seeing things
once they enlist.
Well, okay.
It's a hard environment to adjust to
so I can understand.
But if...
if you feel like it's too difficult
to handle
you must come to me before you think
of doing anything rash.
No, ma'am. I'm really okay.
No, you don't look okay.
That's why I'm saying it.
- Mun-ik.
- Private First Class Tak Mun-ik.
- Has he eaten?
- Not yet, ma'am.
Get him some food first.
Yes, ma'am.
LEFTOVER FOOD SIGNAL
BAD
COOK SOLDIER'S PLEDGE
WITH DUTY AND DEVOTION
I WILL COOK TO BOOST
MY COMRADES' HEALTH AND STRENGTH
TAKE ONLY WHAT YOU CAN EAT!
What is this supposed to be today?
Braised potatoes.
Do you think I'm asking
because I don't know what it is?
I mean, is this a potato?
Or was it one at some point?
It looks like it's been
chewed up and spat out.
What?
I mean...
I'm asking for anything fancy.
Please just make something
that's at least edible.
I think this is supposed to be...
like mashed potatoes, isn't it?
It's American-style.
Next.
Hey, Yoon Dong-hyun is the cook.
How is he getting bigger?
Didn't you see him lifting pork
as weights the other day?
And for his meals
I hear he only picks out the tofu
and chicken breast to eat.
It seems he's a kitchen soldier
not to cook
but to get his protein.
This tastes like shit.
VIGILANCE IS OUR MISSION
Pretty soon, you'll be crying
that you want to go home.
- Wanna go home? Should I call a cab?
- No, sir.
You think any of us were born
here in Ganglim?
You better brace yourself
before we go into the mess hall.
Something straight out of hell
is waiting for you in there.
VIGILANCE THOROUGH AND MISSION PERFECT
Sirs.
Hey, the new guy's here.
Squad 3, Squad 1.
Isn't he ours this time?
KANG SEONG-JAE ROK ARMY
Man, we're screwed again.
Not another smiley face.
Is this a dumping ground?
Why do we only get guys like him?
Tell me about it.
- Hey, TMI.
- Private First Class Tak Mun-ik.
Is that the new recruit?
Yes, sir.
Thank... thank you for the food.
Thanks for the food.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Let's go.
Damn, they smelled fresh meat.
Go on.
How old is our little newbie?
- Private Kang...
- Keep it down.
Sorry, sir.
- This guy is...
- Was I talking to you?
I'm... sorry, sir.
Private Kang Seong-jae.
I'm twenty-two years old.
You're older than you look.
Did you go to some fancy university?
- No, sir. I worked before enlisting.
- Oh, working.
And what amazing job was that?
- Just... a bit of this and that.
- Oh, "this and that".
So, "it's none of your business," huh?
No, sir. That's not it.
Gosh, just from a few words
I can tell you're a special one.
I swear they handpick
these landmines just for us.
Damn, he's totally green. Hey, TMI.
Private First Class TMI... I mean...
- Tak Mun-ik.
- Not living up to the nickname, huh?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Does a top school make you better?
No, sir. I'll make sure
he's properly trained.
Did you enlist not knowing
how tough army life is?
You think it's over after boot camp
but you see how much time is left
and have no clue how to survive, right?
What can you do? If you can't avoid it...
- You have to enjoy it.
- That's right.
Now, when I press this badge
you have to be happy, no matter what.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Well?
Private Kang Seong-jae.
Guess you're not too thrilled
about meeting such great seniors.
Is that the best laugh you've got?
Private Kang Seong-jae.
- P-Dragon.
- Private Pyo Ji-yong.
This is so much fun.
I'm so excited.
What are you doing?
He looked so tense
so we were just messing with him.
If you're bored, go peel some onions.
- TMI.
- Private First Class Tak Mun-ik.
Take the new recruit over there
and eat quietly.
Understood.
He's the top dog of our outpost
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun.
You can tell he's someone
not to mess with, right?
Physically, I mean.
No, sir. He looks like a nice guy.
He is a nice person.
As long as he's not the cook.
Sorry, what was that?
Control your expression while you eat.
He's watching.
Hey, hey, hey!
Get a grip, will you?
Sorry.
So, how is it?
Makes boot camp slop
seem gourmet, doesn't it?
What can you do?
Even though today's is a bit salty
this is one of the edible batches.
What is this?
What?
Help me!
What are you doing?
- It's too salty...
- "Salty?"
Look at this punk complaining.
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun,
did you hear that?
The rookie says the food you made
tastes bad,
and dissing you right to your face.
What do you think about that, sir?
If you don't like it,
you can cook it yourself!
You can cook it yourself!
Oh, no, sir.
I'm sorry.
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT: HWANG SEOK-HO
AWARD CERTIFICATE,
CERTIFICATE OF COMMENDATION
These beans are from a friend of mine
who grows them in Kenya.
It's...
The aroma is just different.
You'll be surprised when you try it.
Well...
I really only drink instant coffee.
A lot of soldiers enlist
with this vague sense of dread.
Seong-jae.
You're a little scared, aren't you?
Private Kang Seong-jae. No, sir.
Well, the military shown in the media
is often quite violent
so I can see why you might think that.
But the truth is...
that's just unbelievable
in this day and age, right?
Now a Sergeant's salary is one million won
it's not the old days of brute force.
Things have changed completely.
Isn't that right, Master Sergeant?
Yes, that's right. In any case...
these days, in the army
soldiers study for entrance exams
and even pass the civil service exam.
Some people
can't perceive the unique aroma
and taste of coffee.
and will only say it's bitter, won't they?
It's not that I dislike good coffee.
I just prefer the instant mix.
But if you concentrate a little more...
sometimes you can smell a floral scent
and sometimes, you can even smell
the earth that grew the fruit.
Seong-jae, as your Company Commander
I think coffee is a lot like the military.
Just a thought, you know?
You can have a mediocre time here, or...
you could have a major
turning point in your life.
Here.
Thank you, sir.
So your mother runs a food truck?
Yes, sir.
There's something so romantic
about street food.
So, what kind of food
does your mom make?
American West-style Chinese food?
Or Mexican tacos and burritos?
She sells tteokbokki.
Oh, and fried snacks and sundae as well.
So, Tteok-Sun-Twi?
Let's make him a cook.
What?
Hero.
Isn't there an open spot?
The Chef's Path tutorial has begun.
Make him a cook?
Sir, isn't that a bit much?
- Why is that?
- What do you mean, "Why"?
Hero.
The fate of this world is in your hands.
From this moment on
your journey to become The Legendary Chef
begins.
That place is full of incidents
and accidents
If we send a kid like him there
for no good reason...
High risk, high return, Master Sergeant.
I, Hwang Seok-ho,
am a man who enjoys taking risks.
Who knows?
This could make our Kang Seong-jae
a great chef, every bit
as good as his mother.
Hey, what's the best dish you can make?
- I can make ramyun, sir.
- Ramyun.
- Making good ramyun isn't easy.
- Ramyun...
Eyeballing the water level...
it's not easy without a natural gift.
- Ramyun!
- It's absolutely not easy.
Okay.
You're going to be a kitchen soldier.
Thank you for your service.
Private Kang Seong-jae!
Sir! Yes, I can!
I will do my best, sir!
Ramyun...
ROK ARMY
KANG SEONG-JAE
Kang Seong-jae.
Private Kang Seong-jae!
What did you do before enlisting?
I delivered water and worked nights
at a convenience store.
What's First In, First Out?
It's ordering items by expiry date
so the older ones get sold first.
Oh, good.
In that case...
organize all these provisions
using First In, First Out.
You mean everything here, sir?
Was I unclear?
No, sir. I'll get right on it.
That's right.
Get started.
- I'm heading out.
- Yes, sir.
Salute!
Good luck.
Yes, sir.
Hey, are you trying to pick a fight
with me right now?
You sent a high-risk soldier
to the outpost with live ammunition?
It's not the first time
we've had one of those guys around.
How are we supposed to screen out
those who are struggling?
Besides.
Managing the soldiers is your job,
isn't it, Master Sergeant?
Don't try to pin the responsibility
for personnel decisions on us.
What are you talking about?
He's depressed and addicted to games.
The kid just got back
from mourning his father, and what?
He's an ace?
You call that an "ace"?
What are you gonna do
if this blows up in our faces again?
Anyway, you pull something
like this one more time
my patience will have its limits.
Listen, Master Sergeant.
Things are already tense at battalion HQ.
Aren't you going too far?
That's your problem, not mine.
Got it?
Damn, what is with this guy?
Oh, hello.
I guess the Personnel Officer
isn't in yet.
Oh, right.
He's swamped with all the
personnel transfers.
Congratulations in advance.
I heard you're getting promoted.
Oh, thank you.
It's just a change in rank insignia
but I already feel the weight.
That must be a lot of pressure.
It comes with the territory.
Things have been too chaotic for a while
so I'll try to handle things
quietly and efficiently.
By the way, is something the matter?
Your voice was booming
which is unlike you, Master Sergeant Heo.
It's...
- the Administration & Supply NCO
- Oh.
- Master Sergeant Park Jae-young?
- Yes.
He's raising hell,
saying the new recruit is unfit.
Goodness, that guy's at it again, huh?
I don't get why everyone
in the 4th Company is so quick to blame.
Seeing you so upset, Master Sergeant Heo
how can I just stand by and do nothing?
Where are you going?
I can't just let this go.
We're not their punching bag.
How am I supposed to organize all this?
Jeez.
How long has this been here?
You've gone from an ordinary hero
to a Kitchen Assistant.
USER INFORMATION
You are currently
Kitchen Assistant, Level One.
GANGLIM OUTPOST
173CM/59KG AB RH(+)
NAME: KANG SEONG-JAE
AGE: 22
INFORMATION
What is all this?
You can use the basic skills
Organizing Ingredients & Chef's Eye.
SKILLS
Well begun is half done.
Your first quest will now begin.
USE A SKILL: ORGANIZE THE STOREROOM
REWARD: 100 EXPERIENCE POINTS
Damn it.
I told him to come inside
when it's time to eat.
INSPECTION
Salute.
There's still grease here.
Are you even cleaning or not?
Who told you to leave
wet rags out like this?
If this causes a norovirus outbreak
and food poisoning
will you take responsibility?
You need to dry these out
completely in the sun.
Yes, sir.
This is why the higher-ups
are losing sleep over Ganglim.
I know guard post life is tough,
but isn't this going too far?
Did you report it to the Master Sergeant?
- That I'm here?
- Master Sergeant
went for supplies.
He's not just hiding out
and slacking off somewhere, is he?
Does he still knock back
bowls of makgeolli on duty?
And what's the Outpost Commander doing?
Right.
- Salute!
- When was this fridge last cleaned?
About that, sir.
I'm the only one managing
the mess hall, so...
Refrigerator condition, unacceptable.
Sir, what brings you here
without any notice?
It's a surprise inspection.
Should I have sent an announcement?
If the kitchen looks like this
I can only imagine the storeroom.
- What do we do?
- What is it now?
The new recruit
- is in the storeroom.
- What?
Salute!
- A Private?
- Private Kang Seong-jae.
Damn.
This unit has gone completely insane, huh?
A brand new recruit is organizing?
What could he possibly know?
You all are unbelievable.
From the inventory,
organized with military precision...
to the bags of rice, perfectly spaced
from the wall to prevent dampness...
It's perfect.
You didn't happen to get
the inspection checklist...
ahead of time, did you?
Of course not, sir.
I only just learned you were here.
Why leave a Private by himself?
What if something had happened?
And then you'd be first to complain
about the soldier's welfare.
What's that supposed to mean, sir?
What I'm trying to say is...
managing your soldiers is also
part of managing the kitchen.
Pay attention.
Do I have to spell it out for you?
In any case...
this is all a mess.
A complete mess!
From now on
let's try to get along.
We're one family in this battalion.
Oh, "family."
What kind of family
just barges in unannounced?
You still haven't figured out
why you were sent here.
- Of course I know.
- And you still act this way?
Just do your job right.
Ye-rin.
Salute.
So...
what's going to happen to us?
If he reports this
to the Company Commander
we will lose our leave.
I didn't know I had leave to lose.
- Yoon Dong-hyun.
- Quest complete.
You have completed
"Organizing the Storeroom."
YOUR KITCHEN ASSISTANT
LEVEL HAS INCREASED
Come on, get a grip, Seong-jae. Okay?
ORGANIZING INGREDIENTS
Get it together.
What the...
Something just...
Why is this so light?
LEVEL UP AND GROW STRONGER
WITH A VARIETY OF SKILLS
Level up and grow stronger...
with a variety of skills.
Levels? Skills?
This isn't a video game.
Do you want to use The Chef's Eye?
The Chef's Eye.
While focused
close your eyes.
Take a deep breath
and open your eyes.
The Chef's Eye
will automatically activate.
SEAWEED, RAMEN, NOODLES
COOKING OIL, FLOUR, CANNED TUNA, RICE,
SEASONING, SWEET CORN
SPAGHETTI SAUCE, SALT, SUGAR,
KETCHUP, TONKATSU SAUCE, SOY SAUCE...
APPLE CIDER VINEGAR
Apple Cider Vinegar.
Origin, Osan Factory, Gyeonggi.
Wait, that thing from earlier...
This is past its expiration date.
It needs to be discarded.
It really works?
After making meals daily,
I have afternoon duties.
Quest complete.
- When am I supposed to do that?
- Gained 100 experience points.
- I work the night shift with no sleep.
- Level up.
What are you doing?
I thought I saw a bug flying around.
Well, of course.
This place hasn't been cleaned properly.
Seong-jae?
Private Kang Seong-jae.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Yes, ma'am.
Get going, you idiot.
Run, you idiot! Hurry!
MY GROWTH ENVIRONMENT
PERSONNEL RECORD CARD
All right.
I heard what happened, more or less.
The Company Commander tends to be
impulsive and just acts on his moods
so I bet you're confused about
how you ended up as a Cook.
Right?
Yes, ma'am.
That's the army for you.
- Just do your best.
- View a new recipe.
Besides, you were
cleaning up well earlier.
But what have you been
staring at this whole time?
Are you possessed by some spirit
claiming you're going to meet
General MacArthur or something?
I go to church.
That's a relief, then.
We've had guys
say things like that before.
I was just checking.
Does that happen often?
Well, not often,
but we get guys like that sometimes.
You know, suddenly seeing things
or hearing voices.
VIEW NEW RECIPE
What?
Why did the Support Section Chief come?
According to the Outpost Commander
he did a surprise inspection
and tore through the kitchen and storage.
Those sons of bitches.
All because I told off
Master Sergeant Heo.
They come crawling back here
being all petty
and start trouble in the mess hall
for no reason.
Is the Company Commander
going to lose his shit again?
Of course he is.
You think a guy who loves raising hell
is going to pass this up?
He's already jealous his peer made Major
so his bitching has tripled.
Now he's complaining
I don't know anything about coffee.
If he studied as much as he complains
about coffee, he'd be a Major by now.
But about that new recruit.
What? Did that kid
already get into trouble?
No. He looks fine, handsome even, but...
Sometimes his gaze is unfocused
and I get a bad vibe from him.
He was acting weird
during the inspection, too.
He blurted out his rank and name
and started looking all around.
You saw it too, didn't you,
Master Sergeant?
You don't think he's going
to cause any trouble, do you?
Come on. It's always the same guys
who act crazy or play sick at first.
We see it all the time.
But that kid, Kang Seong-jae...
is like a landmine.
He's a ticking time bomb.
Hey, does the paperwork ever lie?
No, it has not, sir.
Why would the Company Commander
put that guy in the kitchen?
Hey.
Make it clear to Yoon Dong-hyun.
Kang Seong-jae must not hold a knife.
Here, use this.
Oh, thank you.
I thought you were all skin and bones
but you've actually got
some real muscle on you.
But you know you need more than
just the hardware, right?
When it comes to cooking,
what's really important
is the software that figures out
how the ingredients work together.
Is that right?
You know the biggest mistake
rookies like you make when cooking?
They get excited and start throwing
everything in together.
They end up with slop that
even the army cats won't touch.
Man.
You'll figure it out
as your service goes on.
Use it and bring it back.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
Tell me.
I checked him out.
He's got depression, a gaming addiction...
He's the complete
"high-risk soldier" package.
Then why bring him to the kitchen?
Are they out to ruin a career? Damn it.
The Company Commander thinks the kitchen's
an easy place to dump him.
So watch yourself.
Don't get tangled up with him,
with your discharge so close.
Exactly one hundred days until I'm out.
Just let me make it until then, please.
- Recipe acquired.
- What the...
ACQUIRED RECIPE
BEEF SEAWEED SOUP
Check your new recipe.
Why's he acting like that by himself?
It's so creepy.
I will turn off the lights.
- Have a good night.
- Good night.
Saving system.
Do not shut down.
Let me get some sleep.
I can't sleep.
It's too bright.
Oh, come on.
Just a hundred days.
Just a hundred more days.
GANGLIM
Kang Seong-jae.
Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
Hey, Kang Seong-jae, get up!
Go away.
Is this bastard crazy?
Hey, get up.
A quest... Seriously, what do I do?
- Hey!
- Private Kang Seong-jae.
You punk.
Do you think you're still at home?
Get changed and get out here.
Yes, sir.
Goodness gracious.
BREAKFAST
BEEF SEAWEED SOUP
The Beef Seaweed Soup recipe
is now available.
Make that floor gleam.
You never know
when inspectors might drop in again.
Yes, sir.
I told you, didn't I?
This thing about making food...
It looks like you can just wing it
but... you see... this...
You punk.
Just go buff the floor.
Yes, sir.
AVAILABLE RECIPE
BEEF SEAWEED SOUP
IRONCLAD COASTAL DEFENSE.
UNITED THROUGH CAMARADERIE
SOUP SOY SAUCE, DARK SOY SAUCE
Hey, rookie.
Private First Class Lee Jeong-seok.
What's today's menu?
Today's breakfast is seaweed soup
sausage stir-fry and seasoned seaweed.
Is it Corporal Kim Gwan-cheol's
birthday today?
The menu's killer, sir.
Killer? More like it's so disgusting
it'll make you sick.
Come on, sir. This is a foolproof menu.
But our chef always manages
to fail beyond all expectations.
All right.
Let's survive today!
- Yes, sir!
This isn't a birthday feast.
It's a fatal meal.
I really don't get it, sir.
Is making this that...
hard?
What the hell is this seaweed soup?
The soup is pitch-black.
It looks like it would kill you, sir.
Come on, no way.
It's not like
it's going to actually kill us.
Corporal Kim Gwan-cheol!
Snap out of it!
My bad. Let's move out!
Are you okay?
Is everyone okay?
Corporal Kim.
I want to live, sir!
Are you okay?
Once this battle is over...
I'm gonna go on leave
and tell my girlfriend that I love her.
That's a classic war movie trope.
You look at her picture and die.
You son of a...
- Ji-yong!
Ji-yong!
Just how bad could they make it?
Taste it!
No!
- No!
- Mun-ik... Mun-ik!
I'm alive, sir.
- Mun-ik!
- You bastards!
- Eat it!
Eat it all!
Help me!
This is so gross!
I really can't stand this!
Is cooking really that hard for you?
Go on, try this seaweed soup.
I've never tasted anything like it.
Eat.
You can't be doing this
with the people's tax money.
Do you even taste it before you serve it?
I said, eat.
Stop wasting a spot on a guy like that
and just ask for a decent cook.
If you want to complain so much
you go tell them yourself.
Tell them to pick some
decent guys for a change.
It's not like I asked for the moon.
Is it really that hard for a cook
to cook well?
Damn it!
That punk with seniority thinks
he can treat a senior Sergeant like dirt.
I oughta just...
Looks like everyone's here.
Close up in five.
I'm leaving.
Don't look for me. I'm on edge.
It would be nice
if the rising sun lasted forever...
but after the night passes...
a new sun is bound to rise.
The unit was in the dark for a while...
but it seems the sun
is starting to shine again.
Try to forget about that incident...
and think only of good things.
What do you mean, sir?
You still have so much more to do.
It's just such a shame.
How could he get so greedy
over some cash to end up like that?
Life is unpredictable, isn't it?
He was the most promising cadet
in the academy's history...
and ended up like that overnight.
Who would have ever known?
Jeez.
Anyway, 4th Company Commander.
About the Ganglim Outpost meals.
There were a lot of problems.
Aren't you keeping an eye on things?
What issues are you referring to, sir?
Don't tell me you're not aware.
Based on my personal inspection
the kitchen was in a complete mess.
So it was a surprise inspection.
Honestly, you people...
An army's power comes from its food.
Soldiers' entire day revolves around
wondering what's on the menu
their moods rising and falling with it.
And you can't even manage
to get that right.
I'll take immediate corrective action.
Instead of just that...
If you go from the Baemgol fork,
you'll see Ganglim Outpost, right?
That's right.
It should only take
about an hour to get there.
Why not head over for breakfast?
We can also check on the mess hall.
Be careful on your way down, sir.
Emergency! The Battalion Commander
is on his way to the outpost.
He wants to inspect today's breakfast.
I just finished my duty shift
and on my way home.
Turn the car around, now!
Can't I just go home for once?
- Salute!
- What?
Are you alone? Where's Yoon Dong-hyun?
Well...
He left a little while ago.
Mealtime isn't over. Is he crazy?
Do you not know where he went?
To my beloved.
Present her with a meal
that would make Michelin envious.
To women, a man
who can cook is more appealing
than any other kind of sex appeal.
Just for 99 days.
He made this mess and just took off?
And why is the seaweed soup so black?
Hey, you!
- Hey!
- I'm sorry.
Forget it.
What can I even expect from you?
The Battalion Commander is coming,
and I can't serve this.
A new quest has arrived.
Cooking for the first time is so hard.
Complete the seaweed soup
for the Battalion Commander.
REWARD: 100 EXPERIENCE POINTS
Would you like to use
the acquired Beef Seaweed Soup recipe?
Stop wasting a spot on a guy like that
and just ask for a decent cook.
Who knows?
This could make our Kang Seong-jae
a great chef, every bit
as good as his mother.
Outpost Commander.
Well, if it's all right...
may I try making the seaweed soup again?
Can you cook?
I'm not sure about other dishes
but I think I can make seaweed soup.
You think so?
It's gotta be better than this, right?
All right.
Here, watch this.
I'm going to go change.
Yoon Dong-hyun, that punk.
Just wait till I get my hands on him.
USE ACQUIRED RECIPE?
BEEF SEAWEED SOUP
ADD SEAWEED, MEAT, AND STIR-FRY
Loading recipe.
When rehydrating dried seaweed in water
be careful, as it will
expand significantly.
Stir-fry the beef with sesame oil.
Beef.
What? Why isn't there any?
We used it all this morning.
But can I make seaweed soup without beef?
HIDDEN ITEM
UNKNOWN ITEM
Hidden item. Sea urchin roe
Hero.
Would you like to use
sea urchin roe instead of beef?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO USE
SEA URCHIN ROE INSTEAD OF BEEF?
What's he looking at?
When the broth starts to boil
add soup soy sauce to season.
Found it.
My secret weapon.
By adapting the Beef Seaweed Soup recipe
you have completed
Sea Urchin Seaweed Soup.
SEA URCHIN SEAWEED SOUP.
ADDITION OF GRADE A SEA URCHIN ROE
Creativity score.
An additional half star awarded.
SEA URCHIN SEAWEED SOUP.
ADDITION OF GRADE A SEA URCHIN ROE
Is this really mess hall food?
Do we get sea urchin roe on base?
Yes, sir.
We do.
Well, sometimes
through the local fishermen
we get some very precious sea urchin roe
and make seaweed soup with it like this.
If you use ingredients that aren't
from official military supply
who takes responsibility for that?
All right, now.
I'm starving.
Let's eat first and talk later.
- Let's eat.
- Private Kang Seong-jae! Enjoy!
Enjoy your meal, sir.
What's going on all of a sudden?
Even the Battalion Commander is here.
Mealtime isn't even over.
Where have you been?
I had some milk this morning
and had some stomach trouble.
By the way
who made that?
Who do you think? Kang Seong-jae made it.
What?
Looks like the soldiers left for me.
I should be grateful.
- Battalion Commander.
I'm so screwed.
THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
Do you have any idea
what you've just done?
Nurse, hurry!
- Private Kang Seong-jae.
- Where are you trying to send him?
Complete the Class Change Quest
within 72 hours.
I want to stay on as a cook.
I thought the Company Commander said
to transfer to TOD.
How will you change his mind?
If words don't work
there must be other ways, right?
Why is this so refreshing?
What is it you see in Kang Seong-jae?
Why are you so set on keeping him?
It was an outstanding seaweed soup.
Ending The Chef's Path.